Now we all have realized by this time,
這個時代 我們都獲得了自覺
within us lies the peace, the beauty, the glory of our being.
從而我們的內在有了無窮盡的 平和 美麗和榮耀
There's an ocean of all that.
那裡有無窮無盡的美好
We cannot seek it outside,
我們不能向外去找尋祂 只能向內找尋
what they call in the meditative state,
在所謂的冥想狀態中
you seek it, you enjoy it.
你找到了祂 你享受祂
Like when you are thirsty,
就像口渴時
you go to a river or you go to a ocean,
你會找河流或海洋
and try to quench your thirst.
來解渴
But even the ocean cannot give you sweet water.
但實際上海洋並不能給予你淡水
give you that deep thing that is within you?
給予你內在深入的東西呢
You are trying to find it outside, where it does not lie.
你總想向外找尋 然而祂並不在那裡
It is within us, absolutely with in us.
祂在我們內在 絕對在我們內在
It is so simple because it is your own
要找到祂很簡單 因為祂就在你們內裡
it is within your reach,
垂手可得 就在那裡
What ever you have been doing
你一直以來所做的
going out to find the joy,
都是向外找尋喜樂
the so called joy, the so called happiness,
所謂的喜樂 所謂的幸福
the so called glory of worldly powers and wordly possessions,
所謂的世俗權力和財富的榮耀
you have to reverse it back the whole thing.
現在你必須完全反過來
You have to project within yourself.
讓這些在你內裡呈現出來
It was not wrong that you went out,
向外找尋並非錯誤
it was not correct
向外找尋並非正確
shouldn't feel sorry for what you have done so far.
你不用為所做過的事情感到難過
It was not the correct way
那並不能令你達到生命的 真正喜樂和生命的真正榮耀
It has worked in so many people
祂已在很多人身上運作
that you have entered into that subtler understanding.
由此你們進入了精微的認知當中
Some people are only at a mental level, maybe, doesn't matter.
也許一些人只在思維層面接受了祂 這沒關係
Maybe, some are only at a physical level that they can feel it,
也許一些人只在身體層面感知到祂
doesn't matter. But, you are on the correct lines
這也沒關係 無論如何 你在正確的道路上
you are moving correctly.
向著正確的方向前進
Try to meditate,
試著入靜冥想
meditate more so that you reach your inner being.
多點入靜冥想 從而能達到你內在的存有
And this inner being, is the vast ocean of bliss,
這個內在的存有 是浩瀚無邊的極樂海洋
which exists in every one of us.
存在於我們每一個人之內
Is that vast glorifying flood of light
那個浩瀚壯麗的洪流之光
that floods everybody's inner beauty.
使每個人的內在美流溢出來
So to approach it,
所以為了達到祂
you have to go within yourself by denying things,
你必須向內找尋 並拒絕那些
which are against it, against your movement.
違背衪 違背你升進的事情
Sometimes the wind can be very, very strong for you
有時狂風乍起
to misunderstand
讓你對內裡的神之榮耀有所誤解
The turn back,
折回時
every moment remember that your movement has to be inward.
要時刻記住 你的前進必須是向內的
When you move inward
當你向內深入
you forget the ideas of your outer glories.
你會忘記了那些外在榮耀的想法
A person, who is of a very base nature,
一個很低俗的人
thinks that if he makes a lot of money
認為如果他賺了很多錢
then he has achieved joy, but he has not.
他就能得到快樂 但是他並沒有得到
He's the most unhappy person, if you go and see him.
如果你去看他 會發現他是最不快樂的人
He's worried about small, small things of life.
他擔憂生活中的各種瑣事
You must have heard that people who are very rich
想必你聽說過非常富有的人 會有偷竊癖
They're worried, they're very miserly,
他們憂心忡忡 而且非常吝嗇
they're worried about a needle here and there.
他們擔憂各種針大的小事
A little thing missing they get upset.
哪怕丟失一樣小東西 也會讓他們不安
They have so many habits that they can't live without it.
他們有很多習慣 他們的生活少不了這些習慣
So riches have brought always a curse on human beings.
所以財富帶給人類的 始終是一種詛咒
So those who seek only the riches
所以那些只追求財富的人 並不能享受財富
Then there are some better people,
此外有一些更聰明的人
who think that by ruling others,
他們認為通過支配別人
by getting power, they can achieve
通過獲得權力 他們會在此生謀得一個很好的職位
they too assume, fail.
他們這樣認為 但失敗了
You have seen what happens to them,
你看到過發生在他們身上的事
people don't even want to talk about them.
人們甚至不願意談到他們
Now there are people who get attached to someone
還有一些人 依附著某個人
to one person or to the family, to their children, to their relations,
依附著一個人或家庭
That's also not the way you can get to God,
通過這條路你也不能達到神
that's also so limited,
這條路是如此狹隘
keeps you hanging round them
讓你圍著他們轉
and wasting your energy completely.
完全浪費你的能量
But if you enter into your being fully,
但是如果你完全地進入你的存有
then all these things have such meaning;
所有這些事情都如此有意義
everything has a meaning then.
每件事都會有意義
In a sense if you posses anything,
在某種意義上說就是 如果你擁有什麼
and if you're that kind of a person who is supposed to keep possessing,
你應是那種擁有什麼但從不佔有
He's never possessive; he's so detached about it.
祂從來不想佔有 祂對事物是如此無執著
But, he can play around, because he's so detached,
但是祂能尋找樂趣 因為他如此的無執著
he can create a drama out of it.
祂能從中創造出一齣戲
He can play with the possessions,
祂拿財物開玩笑
and teach lots of lessons to people,
給人們以教訓
He´s so detached, so generous, he enjoys his generosity.
祂是如此不執著
The whole thing becomes so different so dynamic.
整件事情變得如此的不同 如此的有活力
All the beauty that is created by human beings,
人類所創造的美好
as possession is exposed before you
作為財富展現在你面前
and you start enjoying all those things
你開始享受所有那些事物 並不佔有它們
You understand the myth of possession.
你明白了財富的虛幻
Same with your powers that people have over other people.
對於有些人利用你的權力 淩駕於他人之上 是一樣的道理
Those who try to make money out of Sahaja Yoga,
那些想利用霎哈嘉瑜伽賺錢的人
or want to have a kind of a privilege over Sahaja Yoga
或者想在霎哈嘉瑜伽中 擁有某種特權的人
can be subtle, this can go very far.
是非常精明的人 他們這樣會走得非常遠
This subtlety goes to this extent
這種精明到了如此的程度
that I've seen people try to save money on account of Sahaja Yoga.
我看到人們 試圖為了霎哈嘉瑜伽省錢
That's also the attention is on money.
那也是注意力在金錢上
To make money or to save money,
賺錢 省錢
to make a business out of Sahaja Yoga is all absurd,
利用霎哈嘉瑜伽做生意都是荒謬的
but if you say so I say, "All right go ahead for a while,
但是如果你們這樣說的話
Of course Sahaja Yogis can work together,
當然霎哈嘉瑜伽士可以一起工作
can do some business, but Sahaja Yoga is no business.
可以做一些生意 但霎哈嘉瑜伽沒有生意可做
Is business of God,
這是神的生意
where you have to give everything that you have,
你必須為之付出你所有的一切
not ot be attached to anything,
不要執著於任何事物 不要執著
There's no money to be paid as such,
這本身不需要支付金錢
but all your heart has to be poured into it.
但你必須全心全意投入其中
If you cannot pour your heart into it
如果你不能全心投入
you cannot achieve.
你就不能得到
Same about power.
權力也是一樣的
Some people think
有些人認為
that they can even overpower Sahaja Yogis,
他們甚至能夠淩駕於 霎哈嘉瑜伽士之上
impress them, control them,
令他們欽佩 控制他們
such people are thrown out of Sahaja Yoga completely.
這樣的人會被完全地甩出 霎哈嘉瑜伽
You have to enjoy the power of love,
你必須享受愛的力量
that people see you as their protector,
人們會把你當作他們的保護者
as their help, as their support,
他們的幫助 他們的支持和他們的朋友
than somebody who is a dominating personality.
而不是一個專橫的人
You have to be a father head and not a demonic destructive force,
你要做一個父輩般的頭領
which is always threatening everyone.
總是在威脅著每個人
Such people will be thrown out of Sahaja Yoga in no time.
這樣的人很快會被甩出霎哈嘉瑜伽
You are found out.
你是被揀選出來的
I have  no sympathies with such people, never,
我對於這種把你往下拉的人 絕沒有一點同情心
Keep your self aloof with them,
讓自己遠離他們
otherwise when they are thrown away as tangents from Sahaja Yoga
否則當他們沿著霎哈嘉瑜伽的 切線方向被甩出去時
you might get out with them,
你也會和他們一道離開
so be careful.
所以要當心
Then those people who waste all their time
而那些浪費所有時間
just thinking about their family, this thing,
只是考慮他們的家庭 這些 那些的人
or those who have never thought of their family,
或者那些從不考慮他們的家庭的人
also come to Sahaja Yoga.
都來到了霎哈嘉瑜伽
This is a very subtler ground
由於這個非常微妙的原因
on which they can loose their attention to their Spirit.
他們失去了對自己靈體的注意力
They spoil their children, they spoil their husbands, they spoil their wives.
他們寵壞自己的孩子 寵壞自己的丈夫
The whole attention goes in a wrong way
所有注意力都走偏了
and it becomes a very important issue with them,
有些事成為他們很重要的問題
how the marriages are successful, how the children are this thing, that thing.
婚姻是否成功 孩子是這樣還是那樣
They don't leave it to God.
他們沒有把這些交給神
They have to leave it to God. We are all Saints,
他們必須把這些交給神 你們都是聖人
you have to leave every thing to God.
你們必須把一切交給神
In the beginning in Sahaja Yoga everybody says,
剛開始進入霎哈嘉瑜伽時 每個人都說
"My husband is like that, my wife is like that, my brother is like that,
我丈夫是這樣 我妻子是那樣
my children are like this. Mother look after them,"
我孩子是那樣 母親請照顧他們
all right in the beginning, is all right.
剛開始時 這樣沒問題
When you grow you must get out of it.
當你成長時 你要避免這樣
It's an individual journey towards God when you meditate,
這是通往神的個人旅途 當你入靜冥想
and when you reach there then you become collective.
當你到達神那裡時 你便成為集體性的
Before that, it's an absolute individual journey within,
在那之前 這是一條絕對孤獨的內在旅程
absolutely individual journey.
是絕對孤獨的旅程
You should be able to see this.
你應該明白這點
You are in this journey nobody is your relation
在這個旅途中 沒有人是你的親戚
nobody is your brother, nobody is your friend,
沒有人是你的兄弟 沒有人是你的朋友
you're absolutely alone,
你完全孤獨
absolutely alone.
完全孤獨
You have to move alone within yourself.
你必須獨自往內在前進
Don't hate anyone, don't be responsible,
不要憎恨任何人 不要將責任包攬上身
but in meditative mood you're alone.
在冥想狀態中你是孤獨的
No one exists there, you alone,
沒有人在那裡 你是孤獨的
and once you enter into that ocean
一旦你進入到那海洋當中
then the whole world becomes your family.
整個世界就變成了你的家庭
The whole world is your own manifestation.
整個世界變成了你本身的顯現
All the children become your children
所有小孩都成為你自己的孩子
and you treat all people with equal understanding.
你會以無分別心來對待每個人
The whole expansion takes place when you enter inside your Spirit
當你進入你的靈體之內 整個擴展便開始了
and see starting through the eyes of the Spirit.
你會透過靈體的眼睛來看
Such calm, such peace, such bliss exists within you.
在你內裡是如此寧靜祥和 充滿喜樂
You have to be ready for that journey.
你必須為那旅途作好準備
That journey is alone in your meditativeness
在你的入靜冥想狀態中 那旅途是孤獨的
and the more you find something in your meditation
你在冥想中獲得的越多
the more you want to go and distribute it to others.
你想去分享給別人的就越多
That has to,
那是必須的
if that does not come into you then it has not worked out.
如果這還沒在你身上發生 那麼事情還沒成就出來
There is no purity, there's some sort of a bias.
你所分享的東西並不純粹 會存在一些偏見
In that individual pursuit, what ever you find,
在孤獨的追尋中 無論你得到什麼
you want to enjoy it with others,
你想要與別人一起享受
want to give it to others.
你想給予別人
This is the sign of a person who has been really meditating.
這是一個人已經真正進入 冥想狀態的跡象
The one who is meditative
如果一個深入冥想的人
and has not been able to distribute  what he has found,
不能分享他所獲得的
is cheating himself and cheating others as well.
那就是欺騙自己 也欺騙別人
Because that joy that you receive in your meditation
因為你在冥想中獲得的喜樂
has to be distributed, has to be given, has to be shown.
必須要分享 要給予 要展現出來
It should flow in your being
它應該就像從每盞照明燈 發出的光一樣流經你的存有
We don't have to take a vow
我們無需發誓
to say this is an enlightened light,
說這是一盞點亮的燈
in the same way,
同樣地一個聖人也不需要 被證明他是一個聖人
The depth you achieve within yourself spreads all over,
把你內裡所獲得的深度 完全散發開去
it is such an action and reaction.
它就是這樣一個行為和一個反應
The more deeper you become the radiation is much more.
你變得越深入 散發得就越多
A simple person, very ordinary person,
一個簡單的人 非常普通的一個人
uneducated person, can be like that.
沒有受過教育的人 可以達到那樣
We have you know, one gentleman called Vardic in Bombay
你知道我們在孟買 有一名紳士叫Vardic
he's an old man, he's so deep, he radiates.
他是一位老人 他是如此深入 他散發著光
People depend on him, he radiates love,
人們信賴他 他散發著愛 他冥想得如此深入
You don't have to spend too much time on meditation,
你不需要花太多時間 在入靜冥想上
but what ever you spend time, what ever you gain
但是你所花的時間 你所獲得的
is has to be visible outside,
必須是外在看得見的
how you radiate and how you give it to others.
通過你怎樣散發 通過你怎樣給予別人
That's the quality of the saints you have to be.
那就是你要成為的聖人們 必須擁有的特質
Unless and until you become deeper, we cannot save other Sahaja Yogis
除非你變得深入
and we cannot save those who are not Sahaja Yogis.
我們也不能拯救 那些非霎哈嘉瑜伽士
You have to rise higher and higher to pull the whole curtain up.
你必須升進得更高更高 以拉開整個帷幕
Those who try to rise higher
那些想升進得更高
pull the whole thing upward
並向上推動整件事情的人
and they give a pull to everyone who ascend with them.
他們拉了一把 與自己一道升進的每個人
So just try to keep your aim clear cut.
所以要保持你們的目標明確
Must understand what is your aim in life as Sahaja Yogis.
必須明白 作為霎哈嘉瑜伽士 你的人生目標是什麼
Now you are changed people.
現在你們是已轉化了的人類
You are no more people who have to deal with possessions
你不再是那些要處理財物
worry about them, about mundane things, about your livelihoods.
或擔憂財物 擔憂俗事和擔憂生計的人
You are no more people who have to worry too much
你不再是為自己的健康和財物
You are not to worry also about your jobs so much,
你也不應太擔心你的工作 那並不重要
and last of all not to worry about your family,
最後 你也不會擔心你的家庭 孩子 丈夫和妻子
and find a pocket for you to hide into it.
不會找個口袋把自己藏進去
Because the only thing where you can really hide yourself
因為你唯一可以真正藏身的
is the love of God, where you can really get
是神的愛 在那裡你真正得到了
the great restful, blissful, feeling
在衪完全保護之下的 美妙放鬆感和幸福感
Sydney has done very well before and it's progressing better,
悉尼集體以前已經做得很好 現在也進展良好
but the pace is not as it should be.
但還沒有達到其應有的發展速度
So we have to think of new ways and methods
所以我們必須想想傳播 霎哈嘉瑜伽的新方式和新方法
But first you must assume your positions as you are.
但首先你們 必須承擔你們應盡的責任
You must assume that you are all saints
你們必須假設你們都是聖人
that you have to do great work -
所以你們要做偉大的工作
not the ego part of it, but the manifestation of it.
不是自我這麼想 而是真正顯現出來
Every one of you has to decide for oneself.
你們每個人都要下定決心
I'm sure it's going to work out,
我保證它會成就出來
and this time My visit is going to help you a lot by understanding
我的這次來訪 對你們會有很大的幫助
what is the best to spread this light all.
你們會領會這種 讓光到處傳播的最好方法
May God bless you.
願神保佑你